[{"answer": "Well, I think the key revelation, Piers, is that it's really sort of in total of the book this is a book about how she would govern.", "docId": "140210pmt", "aSentId": 34, "question": "What to you is the key revelation you would like to communicate to the outside world which defines this woman, Hillary Clinton?", "qSentId": 33}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "140210pmt", "aSentId": 51, "question": "Am I surprised that people like the late Senator Ted Kennedy or John Kerry or Claire McCaskill are on this hit-list given that they were effectively opposition to them?", "qSentId": 50}, {"answer": "Exactly, exactly.", "docId": "140210pmt", "aSentId": 80, "question": "Isn't it Amie, there's no difference?", "qSentId": 79}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "140210pmt", "aSentId": 97, "question": "Are you sure of that -- or it's in the documents?", "qSentId": 96}, {"answer": "Well educated ones, Piers.", "docId": "140210pmt", "aSentId": 106, "question": "I mean, do they?", "qSentId": 105}, {"answer": "I don't think it matters.", "docId": "140210pmt", "aSentId": 118, "question": "Do the American people still care about Monica Lewinsky enough to punish Hillary at the ballot box because of something Bill did nearly two decades ago?", "qSentId": 117}, {"answer": "Well, we tell the story.", "docId": "140210pmt", "aSentId": 141, "question": "When you did this book and when you finished it, what do you think are the key negatives that you discovered against Hillary Clinton that people may think about and latch on to when they vote?", "qSentId": 140}, {"answer": "Not guilty.", "docId": "140210pmt", "aSentId": 157, "question": "Guilty or not guilty?", "qSentId": 156}, {"answer": "I think pretty significant, you know, we point in the book that she doesn't really have many marquee achievement.", "docId": "140210pmt", "aSentId": 168, "question": "So how significant could that be when it comes to determining who actually gets the Democratic nomination?", "qSentId": 167}, {"answer": "Well I was taking a shower like a normal routine.", "docId": "140210pmt", "aSentId": 192, "question": "First of all, what happened in the bathroom?", "qSentId": 191}, {"answer": "Well, we were going to dinner, we we're on the fifth floor going down to the first floor and I was my pilot Nick Cunningham and two of our mechanics that work on our sleds.", "docId": "140210pmt", "aSentId": 206, "question": "What happened?", "qSentId": 205}, {"answer": "No, I, you know, I think it's just a misfortunate of situation in both scenarios.", "docId": "140210pmt", "aSentId": 211, "question": "Are you always this accident prone?", "qSentId": 210}, {"answer": "Well, our four-man had been in his one of the last events of the Olympic games and so our work started for that competition to get here.", "docId": "140210pmt", "aSentId": 217, "question": "And how are you making sure you don't get trapped again?", "qSentId": 216}, {"answer": "They're very talented group and it's excited to see how much coverage they are getting, and they're going to be one the tougher teams on the hill that, you know, looking at the field of competition, U.S.A. won piloted by Steve Holcomb they're the defending Olympic champions from Vancouver and they're going to be tough, the Russians are going to phenomenal, the Germans, the Canadians, Latvia, Great Britain.", "docId": "140210pmt", "aSentId": 230, "question": "Are you worried about the Jamaicans?", "qSentId": 229}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "140210pmt", "aSentId": 249, "question": "Does that strike you as weird after all this time?", "qSentId": 248}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "140210pmt", "aSentId": 260, "question": "What is the -- I mean, do you have to every single day of your life have people asking you if you're logical?", "qSentId": 259}, {"answer": "No, what they asked me for is to teach them to do the neck pinch.", "docId": "140210pmt", "aSentId": 262, "question": "Well, see other think -- what else do people say to you?", "qSentId": 261}, {"answer": "That's right.", "docId": "140210pmt", "aSentId": 270, "question": "Is it only three seasons of it were ever made the TV show?", "qSentId": 269}, {"answer": "This May.", "docId": "140210pmt", "aSentId": 286, "question": "What was your reaction?", "qSentId": 285}, {"answer": "I quite a long time ago.", "docId": "140210pmt", "aSentId": 289, "question": "Yeah?", "qSentId": 288}, {"answer": "This is an oxygenator.", "docId": "140210pmt", "aSentId": 299, "question": "What is this machine?", "qSentId": 298}, {"answer": "IMOY: That's right.", "docId": "140210pmt", "aSentId": 305, "question": "And that's the breathing issues?", "qSentId": 304}, {"answer": "Pump it up.", "docId": "140210pmt", "aSentId": 311, "question": "Catching oxygen, atmosphere, where's Scotty?", "qSentId": 310}, {"answer": "IMOY: I was smoking a couple of packs a day.", "docId": "140210pmt", "aSentId": 336, "question": "How many were you smoking at your peak?", "qSentId": 335}, {"answer": "He is a lot older than I am.", "docId": "140210pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "Did you hang out together?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "He is.", "docId": "140210pmt", "aSentId": 366, "question": "Is he?", "qSentId": 365}, {"answer": "I haven't seen him in a while now.", "docId": "140210pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "Do you hang out with him?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "You see them all occasionally at \"Star Trek\" gatherings once in a while.", "docId": "140210pmt", "aSentId": 375, "question": "What about the rest of the Enterprise?", "qSentId": 374}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "140210pmt", "aSentId": 380, "question": "ORGAN: You're big on Twitter?", "qSentId": 379}, {"answer": "I'm on there because I have a granddaughter who runs a shop called Shop LLAP, live long and prosper, where she sells \"Star Trek\" related merchandise having to do with me and so forth.", "docId": "140210pmt", "aSentId": 382, "question": "Do you like it as a social piece?", "qSentId": 381}, {"answer": "It's fun.", "docId": "140210pmt", "aSentId": 390, "question": "Is that a bit freaky, that moment when you see them all?", "qSentId": 389}, {"answer": "No, the favorite scene of any of the three seasons.", "docId": "140210pmt", "aSentId": 398, "question": "Ever scene?", "qSentId": 397}, {"answer": "No, no, I have wonderful life.", "docId": "140210pmt", "aSentId": 412, "question": "Well, what are you doing acting -- do you still act at all?", "qSentId": 411}, {"answer": "Yeah, it was a great show.", "docId": "140210pmt", "aSentId": 454, "question": "I mean, we all watch \"Star Trek\", didn't we?", "qSentId": 453}, {"answer": "I'm very good.", "docId": "140210pmt", "aSentId": 456, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 455}, {"answer": "Well, my sixth year is over.", "docId": "140210pmt", "aSentId": 467, "question": "Life, where are you at now with yourself?", "qSentId": 466}, {"answer": "It's a difficult one, you know, because obviously, you know, when these things happen, you think about the families and the people they've left behind, you know, is that what I make it about me.", "docId": "140210pmt", "aSentId": 480, "question": "Did you recognized in him a kind of parallel to what you've been through and how would you advice people to try and help them?", "qSentId": 479}, {"answer": "I think in my case, I mean, I don't know if -- about anyone else.", "docId": "140210pmt", "aSentId": 493, "question": "Is it people that are just -- they have that stricken them about old manner of things not just drugs?", "qSentId": 492}, {"answer": "It's quite an honor to say that about yourself, but, I remember, instead of going to the studio, and you know, everybody was like sort of in recording mode.", "docId": "140210pmt", "aSentId": 536, "question": "What would you think?", "qSentId": 535}, {"answer": "Well, one of the fine things about coming up publicly is that people always encourage you to do it.", "docId": "140210pmt", "aSentId": 550, "question": "What advice would you give to people who are famous and have to come out because that brings with it a particular thing, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 549}, {"answer": "I would say at this point, I don't think I've ever really truly been in love which...", "docId": "140210pmt", "aSentId": 630, "question": "How many times in your life Boy George have you been properly in love?", "qSentId": 629}, {"answer": "... is quite of shocking thing to say.", "docId": "140210pmt", "aSentId": 632, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 631}, {"answer": "I think, yeah.", "docId": "140210pmt", "aSentId": 638, "question": "Do you hope to find true love?", "qSentId": 637}, {"answer": "I would probably -- first, when I played Madison's (ph) (inaudible).", "docId": "140210pmt", "aSentId": 649, "question": "Well, I think -- my second one which is, if I could give you five minutes back or just an hour, whatever it may be to relive the great moment of your life, what would you choose?", "qSentId": 648}, {"answer": "It was two days before Band Aid, but I do it now so much better now.", "docId": "140210pmt", "aSentId": 652, "question": "Early '80s?", "qSentId": 651}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "140210pmt", "aSentId": 664, "question": "I think -- did we do a press stuff?", "qSentId": 663}]